Hananh McCullough

mccullough.hannah@outlook.com | (602) 903-0852 | GitHub

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Innovative full-stack software engineer with skills in building applications & APIs with a user-experience approach. With a curious mind and a background in customer service, management, and athletics, I bring strong skills in client relations, collaboration, and leadership.

SKILLS

Python, JavaScript, React, RESTful APIs, MongoDB, AWS, Git, Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS, DataDog, Microservices, Payments, SQLite, Jira, Banking, Compliance, KYC

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Synapse Financial Technologies (BaaS) Software Engineer II

San Francisco, CA (remote) 07/2022 - 10/2023

- Served as team lead providing technical guidance, mentorship, and knowledge to teammates
- Implemented client direct requests, quick turnaround feature enhancements in RESTful APIs
- Used strong troubleshooting and bug resolution abilities to quickly rectify production API issues
- Managed developer documentation that allowed both internal & external parties to deeper understand the technical side of the products & implementations
- Provided consistent results via strong program design & management skills
- Improved cross-team processes by providing feedback and alternative solutions to leadership, which positively impacted client experience

Freelance Phoenix, AZ 01/2018 - 07/2022

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

- Designed websites for small businesses in the Phoenix area with enhanced UI/UX, resulting in increased traffic and leads
- Designed & created menus, digital catalogs, social media content, and logos using Adobe Photoshop

USAA Phoenix, AZ Insurance Professional I 09/2018 - 11/2022

- Served as a department facilitator in the Pulse initiative by communicating employee feedback & innovation to executives
- Regularly facilitated team meetings, which resulted in an overall increase in team metrics

EDUCATION

Saint Francis University/ Lake Erie college 08/2010 - 05/2014 Bachelor of Arts in Psychology Athlete

Scottsdale Community College 08/2018 - 12/2022 Associates in Applied Science Web Development Web Design

Flatiron School 11/2021 - 03/2022 Certificate Full-Stack Software Engineering